ARMOND ST.JUSTE



FULL STACK SOFTWARE ENGINEER

ABOUT

₱ 555 CEDAR STREET

WEST HEMPSTEAD NEW YORK

TOTAL CONTINUES

WEST HEMPSTEAD NEW YORK

TOTAL CONTINUES

**TOTAL CONTINUES*

☑ ASTJUSTE423@GMAIL.COM

516-640-8416

☐ ITSJUSTEARMOND.ME ☐

ASTJUST1

in ARMOND ST.JUSTE ☑

BACK END

ENTRY LEVEL

NODEJS EXPRESSJS NOSQL DATABASES SQL DATABASES PHP

AWS
GOOGLE CLOUD SERVICES

FRONT END

ENTRY LEVEL

HTML CSS JAVASCRIPT BOOTSTRAP ANGULAR 1 UI/UX

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

ENTRY LEVEL

CONTINUOUS DEPLOYMENT SOFTWARE ARCHITECTURE DATABASE SCHEMA DESIGN WEB SECURITY RESTFUL API WEBSOCKETS

SUMMARY

A Full Stack Software Engineer with 1+ year of professional experience. Currently works with Angular and Node on the front end and interfacing/improving upon a LAMP back-end. Specializes in learning learning fast by using Computer Science fundamentals to quickly understand unfamiliar systems, and to rapidly produce in the process. Aspires to use his expertise to break mental health stigma and get people the help they so desperately need.

EXPERIENCE

BAR AND CLUB STATS INC.

11/2017 - PRESENT

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

- Sped up admin portal loading times by a factor of 10.
- Fixed a critical data loss issue within a month of starting.
- Spearheaded and Coordinated the implementation of a security feature in our ecosystem.
- Patched major security holes in the legacy API.
- Assuage client concerns during sales meetings.
- Discovered and helped patch iOS design flaws.
- Discovered and helped fix iOS UI/UX flaws.
- Deployed a redis cache as a middleman for repeated high latency requests.
- Added CloudFlare for added security while staying within cost constraints.
- Devising a restructure/overhaul of the back-end system. In order to modernize, and mitigate design flaws due to technical debt.
- Providing technical guidance to the team.
- Porting a legacy admin site to a more modern framework.
- Cleaning the legacy codebase.
- Built out webhooks to interface with third party services. Ex: Stripe.

SONARCLOUD

06/2016 - 01/2017

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING INTERN

SonarCloud leverages the power of technology to modernize PA systems

- Implemented features in their client facing iOS app using mostly Objective-C, and some Swift in the form of CocoaPods packages.
- Supported the CTO and CEO on client installations, by elaborating on technical details and putting them into laymans terms.
- Developed an internal CMS using NodeJS and PostgeSQL on the Backend. With JavaScript, HTML/CSS, and Bootstrap on the Frontend. Tied together with a headless architecture pattern.
- Participated in meetings to discuss product direction, pointed out flaws in certain aspects of the business model.
- Provided alternative business plans with regards to maintaining the product.
- Participated in Pair Programming sessions with the CTO.

EDUCATION

BINGHAMTON UNIVERSITY

08/2012 - 05/2016